‎NETFLIX アニメシリーズ
♪～
～♪
（メイン）
ハア ハア ハア ハア…
Good morning, Night City! Rise and shine
for a new day in the City of Dreams…
（メイン）
ハア ハア ハア ハア…
‎（ラジオ：ＤＪ）
‎ハロー ナイトシティ！
（メイン）
ハア ハア ハア ハア…
‎今日も夢の街で
‎新たな１日が始まるよ！
（メイン）
ハア ハア ハア ハア…
‎今日も仕事に遅刻さ
Got reports of a pile-up
on the Heywood highway.
We've got gonks dreaming of
becoming the next Weyland Boa Boa
‎ウェイランド･ボア･ボアみたいな
‎レジェンドに憧れるアホ野郎が
jamming up traffic for the rest of us!
‎ハイウェイに
‎並んでいやがるからだ～
（メイン）
ハア ハア ハア ハア
…gangoons swarming like flies! What is it
about this City that keeps attracting…
（メイン）
ハア ハア ハア ハア
‎おいおい どうしてナイトシティは
‎こうも連中を引き寄せちまうんだ？
ハア ハア ハア…
Never fear the risk!
‎リスクを恐れるな
‎ド派手な夢をつかみたけりゃ
ハア ハア ハア
You'll never make it big
dreaming quiet, dreaming small.
ハア ハア ハア
‎でかいリターンを
‎勝ち取りゃいいのさ
ハア ハア ハア
Wanna know where
all the legends of Night City play?
ハア ハア ハア
‎ナイトシティの伝説が
‎こぞって集まる場所を知ってるか？
It's…
‎それは…
Maine.
‎（ドリオ）メイン
When's the last time you ate?
‎食ってないだろ メシ
‎チッ
‎（ドリオ）アームの震え
‎神経がやられてきてるんでしょ
You're shaking. All that chrome's
messing with your nerves.
When this's over, you gotta refit.
Go lightspec, reduce your load.
‎これが終わったら
‎負担の少ないクロームに
‎変えたほうがいい
‎（メイン）大げさなんだよ
‎手の震えくれえで
Just some jitters.
Don't make it a big deal.
‎（メイン）大げさなんだよ
‎手の震えくれえで
（注入音）
‎（メイン）大げさなんだよ
‎手の震えくれえで
‎（ドリオ）あんた このままじゃ…
Shit, at this rate…
‎（メイン）
‎チッ インプラントの10や20で！
A lil' metal ain't gonna…
‎んっ！
Maine?
‎（ドリオ）メイン？
‎（メイン）なっ…
‎（ドリオ）おい メイン
Hey! Maine!
Fuck off!
No one's gonna set my limits but me!
‎うるせえ！
‎俺の体のことは
‎俺がいちばん分かってる！
I made it this far without any trouble.
‎この仕事も
‎やっと ここまできたんだ
I ain't gonna turn back now!
‎途中でやめられるかよ！
Where's the fucking data?!
‎まだか データは！
You know Kiwi's diving for it!
‎（ドリオ）今 キーウィが
‎ハッキングしてるだろうが！
‎（キーウィの荒い息）
ICE is thicker than I expected…
‎（キーウィ）思ったより
‎分厚い‎ＩＣＥ(アイス)‎だよ これは
‎（力み）
‎（ズシュ！）
‎（殴る音）
‎（倒れる音）
‎（メイン）ハア ハア…
‎（ドリオ）メイン やめろっ
Maine! Stop! What're you…
‎（殴る音）
‎何をしてんだ おい！
Hey!
‎（メイン）ハア ハア ハア…
Kiwi? Falco?
‎キーウィ？　ファルコ？
‎（ドリオ）
‎ハア… 落ち着いたか クソッ
You back with us? Shit…
‎（メイン）ドリオ
Dorio?
‎何だ　何があった？
What gives? We get jumped?
‎襲撃か？
‎どうしたんだ キーウィのやつ…
（ファルコ）おらあ！
What happened to Kiwi…
…forecast for heavy rainfall on the coast.
‎（ラジオ：お天気キャスター）
‎海沿いの地区では所により雨
Districts like Santo Domingo
and Westbrook,
‎サントドミンゴ
‎ウェストブルックでは
are bound to see showers
from midnight to sunrise--
‎夜半過ぎから明け方にかけて
‎激しく雨の降る時間帯が
‎ありそうです
（ため息）
‎（ホロコール着信音）
‎（デイビッド）ん？
What the fuck, Falco?!
‎（デイビッド）
‎ファルコ 何なんだよ 一体
Ask Maine? Just tell me…
‎は？　メインに聞けって何だよ
‎おおお おい！
Yo!
はあ？
Huh…?
‎（ルーシー）私には無理
I won't do it.
‎あ… キーウィが
‎救急送りって そんな…
How'd Kiwi land on an op table?
She was on Tanaka's case, right?
‎タナカのハッキングだろ？
‎何があったの？
What went wrong?
‎そこのバカに聞きな
Ask the gonk next to me.
‎（メイン）うるせえ
Fuck off.
Maine punched her out. Lost his cool when
she ran into some ICE that snagged her…
‎（ドリオ）メインが殴った
‎トラップにかかったキーウィに
‎腹を立てて
What!?
‎えっ！
Maine. How about you
get your head checked?
‎（ルーシー）
‎メイン あんたが病院行ったら？
‎（メイン）は？
Maine, next time you start losing it--
‎メイン　今度 兆候が出たら…
‎（メイン）チッ！
‎（ドカッ！）
‎（遠ざかる足音）
Hey…
‎なあ 兆候って？
"Losing it"…?
（ドアの開閉音）
‎サイバーサイコシスだ
Cyberpsychosis.
（ドアの開閉音）
‎（注入音）
‎（注入器の落下音）
‎メイン！
Maine!
Uh… Hey.
‎あの… さ
Dorio just told me. You…
‎ドリオが言ってたんだけど その…
‎だ… 大丈夫だよな メインは！
‎あんな…
You'll be fine, right?
You won't end up like…
Fine?
‎（メイン）大丈夫？
What you mean by "fine"? Kid.
‎大丈夫っていうのは何だ？
‎デイビッド
You asking if I'm going psycho?
‎サイバーサイコか？
You think I'm losing it?
‎俺が あんなふうに
‎なるってえのか？
Maine, I didn't say…
‎メイン 俺は…
‎（メイン）
‎つきまとうな デイビッド
Lay off, kid.
‎チョロチョロ走り回って
‎うぜえんだよ
Your snooping around's
getting on my nerves.
‎え…
You think you're hot shit
'cause you're faster than me?
‎サンデヴィスタンで
‎人より速く走れるからって
‎もう一人前面か？
That Sandy was supposed to be mine.
‎そいつは もともと俺んだ
‎（ガラスが割れる音）
I made it this far.
‎（メイン）やっとここまで来たんだ
Ain't no way I'm gonna downgrade now…
‎ここにきて クロームを
‎ダウングレードして何になる？
Can't stop running now…
‎何のために ここまで走って…
‎（ドリオ）
‎もう捜索も始まってるかもしれない
The pigs probably have our trail already.
We only got 'til morning, if that.
‎朝までが勝負なのは分かってるだろ
（ドアが開く音）
Are you hearing me?
‎（ドリオ）やるしかないんだ
‎（ルーシー）できないわ！
I said no!
‎あんたこそホントに分かってるの？
You're the one that's not listening!
He's Arasaka…
‎アラサカの…
Let's call it off.
‎（デイビッド）やめようぜ
C'mon, Lucy.
‎もう帰ろう ルーシー
‎無理してやることねえよ
You don't gotta do it.
Shut it, David!
‎（ドリオ）黙ってな デイビッド
We can drop Tanaka where we took him.
Pretend none of this happened.
‎（デイビッド）
‎タナカを元の所に置いて
‎全部 なかったことにすれば…
You've got a lot of nerve!
‎（ドリオ）
‎あんた いいかげんにしな！
‎おいっ
‎逃げてもしょうがないんだ！
I'm not done with you!
David… Tell me I can do it.
‎（ルーシー）デイビッド
‎できるって言いなさい
Wha… I thought…
‎（デイビッド）
‎はあ？　でも さっきは…
Tell me!
‎（ルーシー）言うのよ！
You don't understand
what Arasaka's like at all.
‎あんた アラサカがどんな所か
‎分かってない
‎見られてるのよ！
They're always watching us. You… me…
‎私も あんたも…
We can't just call it off.
‎やるやらないじゃないわ
‎やるしかないのよ
We don't have a choice.
I know that.
‎分かってるのよ
But… I need you to tell me that I can.
‎でも あんたが言えば 私…
Please…
‎きっと…
I'm sorry, Lucy. I…
‎（デイビッド）
‎ごめん ルーシー 俺…
I know you can do this.
‎できるよ 君になら… いや
I believe in you, Lucy.
‎やるんだ ルーシー
I'll do it.
‎やるわ
What?
‎はあ？
‎（ルーシー）
‎ただしデイビッドと２人でよ
But David's coming, too.
And kick Maine out.
‎メインも入ってこさせないで
‎じゃなきゃ やらないわ
Those are my conditions.
‎あ…
Fine.
‎分かった
But you'll keep us in the loop.
Pings every quarter hour.
‎ただし連絡は入れろ
‎15分おきにだ
You've got until daybreak.
Don't screw this up!
‎夜明けまでに片づけろ いいな
‎ハア
David! Where's Maine?
‎（ドリオ）
‎デイビッド　メインは？
‎ハア…
‎知らねえ
（ホロコール着信音）
Hell if I know!
‎（ノイズ音）
（ホロコール着信音）
‎（メインの足音）
‎（ドリオ）メイン！
Maine!
‎あ… ドリオ？
Dorio…
‎（デイビッド）なあ やっぱり
‎ドリオは いたほうがいいんじゃ…
Hey, you sure we don't need
Dorio for backup?
Grow a spine.
‎（ルーシー）腹決めなよ
Why didn't you…
‎つーか先に…
‎先に言えよ
You should've told me.
Why's it gotta be just the two of us?
‎なんで２人でやらなきゃ
‎いけないんだよ
David.
‎（ルーシー）デイビッド
H-Hey…
‎（デイビッド）あの… さ
‎あ…
Why were you hiding your deep-dive port?
‎なんでディープダイブ用のポート
‎隠してたの？
Jacking in now…
‎（デイビッド）入れるよ
‎（装着音）
David…
‎（ルーシー）デイビッド
‎何？
Yeah?
‎フウ… 行ってくる
I'm going in.
Where there's a trap,
there has to be an entryway.
‎（ルーシー）
‎トラップがあったということは
‎ここが入り口であることは
‎間違いない
‎うっ…
‎フウ
‎（ホロ通信：デイビッド）
‎うん そう　メインは？
‎（ドリオ）‎今は落ち着いてる
‎（デイビッド）
‎なあ ドリオ　こいつさ…
‎（ドリオ）‎何？
‎（デイビッド）‎あ いや 何でもない
We gonna kill him?
‎殺すのかな
We need a plan
in case she doesn't make it.
‎（メイン）
‎時間切れの準備が必要だな
Wouldn't have needed one
if you weren't feeling like shit.
‎（ドリオ）あんたの調子がよければ
‎しなくてもいいんだけどね
‎（ホロコール着信音）
‎（メイン）ん？
‎（メイン）‎何の用だ
‎（ファラデー）‎データは まだか？
‎（メイン）‎今やってる
‎（ファラデー）‎ずいぶん かかるな
‎誰がやっている？
（メイン）
何なんだ 一体
（ファラデー）メイン
隠し事をしているだろ
‎（メイン）‎ああ？
‎（ファラデー）
‎キーウィなしでできるのか？
‎（メイン）
‎なんで… チッ ファルコか
‎（ファラデー）
‎バックアップのランナーには
You're willing to bet everything
on a backup runner?
‎荷が重くないか？
‎（メイン）‎問題ない
Absolutely.
‎（ファラデー）‎とにかく急げ
Tick tock, Maine.
Arasaka is still short one executive.
‎アラサカの重役に
‎直接 手を出したんだ
I trust you understand
there's no room for error.
‎今度こそ失敗は許されない
（メイン）分かってる
Made that clear.
What?!
‎（メイン）何だ！
The fuck you staring at, Faraday?
‎（メイン）何 見てやがる ファラ…
‎（倒れる音）
‎（雨の音）
‎（タナカのせき込み）
‎（ノイズ音）
A glitch…?
‎（ルーシー）‎安定しない？
（タナカのせき込み）
‎クソッ 何だよ いきなり
Damn it… Now of all times!
‎（イスがきしむ音）
W-Wait…
‎（タナカ）ま… 待て　待ってくれ
Wait, please!
David!
‎デイビッド！
‎（注入音）
‎クッ… おい メイン
‎しっかりしろ！
Maine! Snap out of it!
‎おい！
Hey!
Damn it! Why is he waking up?!
‎（ルーシー）
‎クソッ 麻酔が切れかかってる
What are you doing, David?!
‎何やってんの デイビッド！
‎（タナカの荒い息）
I knew it… You're David…
‎（タナカ）やはり君か デイビッド
How do you…
‎どうして…
I've heard much about you.
‎（タナカ）君について
‎いろいろ報告を受けている
Your incident with my son at the Academy…
‎カツオと君の間に
‎問題があったことも知っている
‎ゲホッ ゲホッ ハア…
‎そのうえで
‎君の復学を指示したのも私だ
And despite that, I ordered
your readmittance to the Academy.
‎（デイビッド）あんたが？
You?
‎頼む デイビッド　助けてくれ
Please, David. You can stop this.
I don't want to die.
‎まだ死にたくないんだ
We just need the data. You won't…
‎データを抜き取るだけだ
‎殺されは…
Don't be so naive!
‎そんなわけあるか！
‎ハア… あいつらの顔を見た
I've seen their faces!
Do you believe Arasaka
won't hunt them down?
‎それでも消されないと？
Listen to me.
Why do you think I lifted your expulsion?
‎聞け　なぜ君を復学させたと思う？
You have exceptional abilities.
‎君が貴重な人材だからだ
I believe you could become
a valuable asset to Arasaka!
‎アラサカに利益をもたらすと
‎信じている
We could give you a great future, David!
‎将来は約束されてるんだ
‎デイビッド
Do not throw your life to waste!
‎人生を棒に振るな！
‎（ノイズ音）
This is it.
‎（ルーシー）‎これか
‎ハッ！
‎（データ転送音）
I can't let you go.
‎（デイビッド）
‎あんたを逃がすのは無理だ
Then get in contact with Arasaka.
‎（タナカ）アラサカに通報しろ
It will all be over
in less than five minutes.
‎あとは何もしなくていい
‎５分で片がつく
‎そういう意味じゃない
‎仲間を裏切れない
That ain't what I mean!
I can't betray my crew.
Stupid boy.
Don't you see you're being used?
‎バカが！
‎使い捨てにされるのがオチだぞ
And Arasaka won't?
‎（デイビッド）
‎アラサカに入ったって同じだろ
No. You are blind.
‎（タナカ）違う　分からんか？
Who do you think is paying for this stunt?
‎どうせカネを出しているのは
‎ミリテクだろう
It has Militech written all over it.
All roads lead back to the corporations.
‎お前らは企業の代わりに
‎手を汚しているだけ
Regardless of
how high you climb in this world,
‎その世界で どれだけ上に行こうと
‎しょせんコーポの末端以下だ
you will never amount to the lowest corpo.
That's not…
‎（デイビッド）そんなこと…
‎（ノイズ音）
‎ぐはっ！
‎（メインのせき込み）
‎（ホロコール発信音）
David?
‎デイビッド？
（ホロコール着信音）
‎（タナカ）
‎なあ デイビッド 君は…
David… What…
‎君は本当は何がしたいんだ？
What is it that you want?
‎あ…
‎（デイビッド）何がって…
What do I want…?
（着信音停止）
‎（ドアの強打音）
‎（ドアを破る音）
‎（ドリオ）デイビッド 何してる！
David! What the fuck?!
He's awake!
‎（メイン）起きてるぞ
‎デイビッド 薬は？
Where's his tranq… Hand it over!
‎貸せ！
‎ううーっ！
‎（スパーク音）
Fuck! What just happened?!
‎（警報音）
‎（メイン）クソッ 何が起きた
Shit! It's all over if he flatlines!
‎マズい
‎今 死んだら終わりだぞ！
‎デイビッド！
David!
‎しっかりしろ デイビッド
‎あんたがセッティングしたんだろ！
Snap out of it, David!
You got her in, right?!
‎どうすればいい？
Now get her out!
Dorio! Lucy's still stuck in deep-dive!
‎（デイビッド）ドリオ
‎ルーシーはディープダイブしてる
‎何！
-What?!
-Hurry! Disconnect her!
‎早く 接続切って！
‎（ドリオ）クッ…
‎よし
Alright! Pull her out!
‎抜いて！
‎（注入音）
‎（ボフッ！）
‎ハア…
‎（ルーシー）フウ…
‎（メイン）データは大丈夫か
The data?
‎（ドリオ）心停止して
‎すぐ処置したから たぶん
Jabbed him right after
his heart stopped… so probably good.
David!
‎（メイン）デイビッド！
Yeah, Lucy's--
‎ああ ルーシーも大丈…
‎デイビッド てめえ何やってた！
David! What the fuck were you doing?
What about you?
‎（デイビッド）あんたこそ
What the fuck were you doing?
‎あんたこそ何やってたんだよ！
What did you say?
‎んだと？
Knocking Kiwi out…
Dropping all this on Lucy's lap.
‎（デイビッド）キーウィに当たって
‎ルーシーに全部 押しつけて
What the fuck's been up with you?!
‎何やってたって聞いてんだよ！
Kid, don't start…
‎デイビッド てめえ…
Maine! David!
‎メイン　デイビッド！
‎（メイン）あ？
Jammer got fried when Tanaka flatlined!
Trauma Team caught the signal!
‎さっきので偽装チップがやられた
‎トラウマチームに信号が漏れてる
Motherfuck!
‎（メイン）クソが！
‎（発砲音）
David, we ain't done yet!
‎デイビッド 話はあとだ
‎車の準備をしろ！
But prep our wheels, quick!
‎（発砲音）
‎（殴る音）
Get it together, David!
‎（ドリオ）
‎しっかりしな デイビッド！
‎やるんだろ！　やりな！
You volunteered for this, so do it!
‎（メイン）
‎すぐ行くから下で待ってろ
Wait in the ride. We'll catch up.
I know!
‎（デイビッド）分かってる
‎（インプラント発動音）
‎プラチナ対応ってやつかい
Fucking Platinum premium plan service…
‎ドリオ！
Dorio!
Registering gunfire in the service area.
‎（トラウマ隊員）
‎目標地点付近から発砲音を確認
Possible hostiles present.
Requesting NCPD backup in force.
‎武装した障害が存在する可能性あり
‎ＮＣＰＤ(エヌシーピーディー)‎へ応援要請
‎（ドアが閉まる音）
（エンジン始動音）
（大音量のラジオ音楽）
‎うっ…
（エンジン始動音）
（大音量のラジオ音楽）
‎（ラジオ停止）
‎（ルーシー）デイビッド…
David?
‎あ… ルーシー！　大丈夫？
Lucy! You alright?
What's going on?
‎（ルーシー）何がどうなってるの？
Tanaka woke up, but his brain
suddenly fried for some reason.
‎タナカが目を覚ましたと思ったら
‎脳が焼かれて…
Did something happen in there?
‎中で何かあった？
Where's Maine and Dorio?
‎（ルーシー）メインとドリオは？
‎（デイビッド）
‎タナカを連れてあとから…
They're bringing Tanaka's body…
‎（ルーシー）ん？　死んだんじゃ…
But he's dead.
‎（デイビッド）蘇生させた
We saved him.
‎ハッ… なんで！
Why?!
What do you mean? We still need the data.
‎（デイビッド）
‎なんでって まだデータが…
There's no point bringing him.
‎タナカを連れてきても意味ない
‎データはなかったの
There was no data.
‎えっ…
No way…
‎ウソだろ？
Fuck. We're definitely on
'Saka's radar now.
‎（メイン）クソッ
‎これでアラサカにもバレたな
（注入音）
‎（ドリオ）メイン
‎抑制剤 忘れんじゃないよ
Maine! Don't forget to take your meds!
Just took a shot!
‎（メイン）今 打ったろ！
‎（トラウマ隊員）動くな！
Don't move!
‎（発砲音）
‎（遠くの銃声）
Fuck! Why's NCPD always fast
when it comes to us?
‎（メイン）
‎クソッ ＮＣＰＤのやつら
‎こんな時ばっか仕事が‎早(はえ)‎え
‎奥だ　奥行け！
Back up! Go to the back!
‎（ノイズ音）
Fuck! They won't pick up!
‎クソッ　つながらない
‎（ドアが開く音）
David!
‎（ルーシー）
‎デイビッド どこ行く気？
Where are you going?
Gonna go help.
‎助けに行く
No! What if they slip out another way?
‎バカ！
‎入れ違いになったらどうするの
We're waiting!
‎待つのよ
I'm going.
‎（デイビッド）やっぱり行く
‎（ルーシー）デイビッド！
David!
What are you so afraid of?!
It shouldn't be taking 'em this long!
‎（デイビッド）何ビビってんだよ
‎こんなに時間がかかるなんて
‎おかしい！
Wait!
‎（ルーシー）待って　無線を拾えた
I got a signal. Trauma is here…
alongside the NCPD.
‎トラウマの奥にＮＣＰＤも来てる
‎囲まれてるのよ
They're surrounded.
Then we gotta help.
‎（デイビッド）なおさら行かなきゃ
No! Do you want to die?!
‎（ルーシー）
‎ダメよ　あんた死にたいの？
‎（遠くの銃撃戦の音）
I won't die. I'll come back to you.
‎（デイビッド）死なないよ
‎ルーシーがいるんだから
David…
‎（ルーシー）デイビッド
‎もしかしたら２人とも
‎助からないかもしれない
They might not make it.
We should cut our losses and run.
‎このまま逃げたほうが…
We can still hear them fighting!
They're still alive!
‎（デイビッド）
‎音が聞こえるのに？　まだ生きてる
You're acting weird today, Lucy.
‎今日は様子が変だよ ルーシー
You saw something, didn't you?
In Tanaka's neural net…
‎やっぱ何か見たんだ タナカの中で
I… only wanted to…
‎（ルーシー）私は… あんたに…
Lucy?
‎（デイビッド）なあ ルーシー
‎俺には言ってくれないんだね
Aren't you gonna tell me
‎え？
‎“できる”って
that you believe in me, too?
‎フッ…
‎クッ… ン！
‎ああああーっ！
‎クッ 何やってんだ メイン！
‎ボサっとしてんじゃ…
The fuck, Maine?!
‎クッ 何やってんだ メイン！
‎ボサっとしてんじゃ…
（ノイズ音）
Get it together…
‎（発砲音）
‎（メインのうなり声）
Shit! Fucking gonk…
‎クソッ　あのバカ！
‎（メインの荒い息）
‎（発砲音）
Don't shoot!
‎（トラウマ隊員）‎ダメだ　撃つな
‎（警察官）‎なんでだ！
Why not?!
‎（トラウマ隊員）
‎プラチナメンバーを盾にしてる
He's holding a platinum client hostage!
‎（警察官）‎そんなの知るか！
Not our problem!
‎ぐわっ！
‎（発砲音）
‎（雨の音）
‎ううっ…
‎（発砲音）
‎（倒れる音）
Dorio…
‎（メイン）ドリオ？
Maine… Hold on, I'm on my way.
‎（デイビッド）
‎メイン　今 あんたのとこに行くよ
‎（叫び声）
I need…
‎あんたが
I need you to tell me I can do this.
‎あんたがやれって言えば 俺…
Was this…
‎（メイン）‎俺か？　俺のせいか？
Was this my fault?
Freeze! Weapons down,
hands behind your head!
‎（警察官）動くな！
‎武器を置いて両手を頭の上に上げろ
Last warning!
‎（警察官）聞いているのか！
‎（たじろぐ声）
‎（鎖の切断音）
‎（タナカを投げる音）
Platinum client confirmed dead.
‎（トラウマ隊員）
‎契約者の死亡を確認
‎（メイン）なあ
Hey.
‎う…
‎俺のせいか？
Is this my fault?
‎（グシャ！）
‎（銃声）
‎（トラウマ隊員）サイバーサイコだ
It's cyberpsychosis!
‎（警察官）
‎MaxTac(マックスタック)‎に連絡を… ああっ
Flag MaxTac now…
Got a cyberpsy--
‎（ホロコール発信音）
Client has flatlined. Evacuate!
‎（トラウマ隊員）
‎契約者の死亡確認　撤退だ！
Hey, where are you going?!
‎（警察官）おい どこに行く！
Client policy's void!
This's your problem now!
‎（トラウマ隊員）
‎契約解除だ　もう勝手に撃っていい
Fuck that!
‎（警察官）ふざけんな
‎（銃声）
He's here! Get us out!
‎来たぞ　早く出せ
‎でやあーっ！
‎（爆発音）
‎（トラウマ隊員）ああーっ！
‎うわあーっ！
Shit!
‎（警察官）クソッ！
‎（銃の不発音）
‎（警察官の叫び声）
‎（グシャ！）
‎（ホロ通信：ルーシー）
‎デイビッド 聞こえる？
David… Can you hear me?
Maine's gone psycho.
‎メインがサイバーサイコに…
They've called in MaxTac.
Turn around, come back…
‎MaxTacも呼ばれて…
‎早く戻ってきて
‎（デイビッド）メイン！
Maine…
Oh. Hey, kid.
‎（メイン）なんだ デイビッドか
‎ケガしなかったか？
You alright?
Maine, I came to back you up…
‎（デイビッド）
‎メイン 俺 助けに… いや…
（ボンベを投げる音）
Uh…
Dorio's dead.
‎ドリオがな 死んじまった
What?
‎（デイビッド）
‎え？　何だよ これ
What are you doing…?
Last thing I can do for her.
‎（メイン）
‎それくらいしか してやれねえ
Let's run, Maine.
‎逃げよう メイン
‎あんたも死んじまう
You're gonna die.
No more running. Reaper's calling my name.
‎（メイン）俺は逃げねえ
‎死に神が そこまで来てるんだ
‎（‎ＡＶ(エーブイ)‎の飛行音）
‎（デイビッド）何言ってんだよ
What are you saying?
‎（カチャ！）
Fine. I'll fight too.
‎分かった　俺も戦うよ
Kid…
‎（メイン）デイビッド
I've already made up my mind.
I'll do it! I'll save you.
‎決めたんだ やるって
‎俺がメインを助ける
Damn it! Stop shaking!
‎クッソ… ビビんな！
‎ナメんなよ MaxTacが！
‎来てみやがれ！
Fuck you, MaxTac! Come and get us!
Maine, we can get through this together.
‎メイン　２人なら何とかできる
We'll get through this. And then… then…
‎何とかして…
‎何とかなったら そしたら…
‎（ＡＶの飛行音）
‎（デイビッドの荒い息）
‎（ＡＶの着陸音）
‎（扉が開く音）
‎（隊員たちの足音）
‎（デイビッドの荒い息）
David.
‎（メイン）デイビッド
You can't do it.
‎お前には まだ無理だ
Why… Maine…
‎なんでだ メイン…
Why…
‎なんで…
David.
‎（メイン）デイビッド
‎（ペシッ！）
This is the end of the line for me.
‎俺は ここで死ぬ
‎お前は生きろ
But not for you.
Fast is what you do, remember?
‎人より速く走れるんだろ？
Keep running.
‎走り抜けろ
‎（発砲音）
‎あ… ああああああ…
‎ぐわっ…
‎（爆発音）
（ホロコール発信音）
（ルーシーの震える息）
（バシュン！）
ハッ！
‎（車の走行音）
♪～
～♪